Jemma: I arrive on time.
I’m hoping to have an interesting fun time with someone new.
I see Pietro.
My first impressions are good.
He’s well-dressed and polite.
We talk about all kinds of things: our travels, food, animals, places we’ve lived in, TV shows.
He’s really interesting and funny, and I really enjoy talking to him.
The only problem is, we are talking so much that I don’t notice that my shirt is on fire
– from the candle on the table!
The waiters run to the table to put it out!
I’m not sure what he thinks of me – probably that I’m very talkative!
We don’t have time to go anywhere after dinner, because I need to catch a train home,
but I feel that we need more time together.
We don’t kiss goodbye, but when I’m waiting for my train,
he runs up and gives me a cake from the restaurant to eat on the train!
Perhaps we can meet again and continue our conversation.
Pietro: I arrive hoping to meet someone interesting.
My first impressions are that she’s friendly and talkative, perhaps a bit nervous.
But it’s very easy to chat.
We talk about climate change, travel, TV shows, future plans.
She has good manners,
and she politely asks the waiter if we can move to a quieter table.
I think she loves life, and is very adventurous, and has had a lot of experiences.
I’m not sure what she thinks of me, maybe that I’m a bit young,
but I hope she thinks I’m interesting.
I’m sad that we can’t go somewhere for a drink after dinner,
but she needs to get her train home.
It’s an unforgettable evening.
In fact, truly unforgettable, because during the dinner her shirt catches fire!
I’d really like to meet again.